const data = [
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9de",
        "correctAnswer": "Abraham Lincoln ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Gerald Ford",
          "Herbert Hoover",
          "Ulysses S. Grant"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the 16th president of the USA, in term during the period 1861–1865?",
        "tags": [
          "presidents",
          "usa",
          "leaders",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "645cb16b7d263fd5097043d5",
        "correctAnswer": "El Dorado",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Atlantis",
          "Shangri-La",
          "Camelot"
        ],
        "question": "What fabled city was German adventurer Philipp Von Hutten searching for when he explored South America in the 1540s?",
        "tags": [
          "south_america",
          "exploration",
          "mythology",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95026a",
        "correctAnswer": "Chicken Marengo ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Chicken Kiev",
          "Hunter's Chicken",
          "Chicken Supreme"
        ],
        "question": "Which chicken dish is named after a battle in the Napoleonic wars?",
        "tags": [
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "6497ef4d0752843c0d8aadd5",
        "correctAnswer": "The Bubonic Plague",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Spanish Flu",
          "Smallpox",
          "Cholera"
        ],
        "question": "Which epidemic hit London in the 17th century, killing tens of thousands of people each time?",
        "tags": [
          "diseases",
          "epidemiology",
          "history",
          "london",
          "1600s",
          "1600's"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "63a039bcc7d86251f9b65ca9",
        "correctAnswer": "St. Augustine, Florida",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Boston, Massachusetts",
          "New York, New York",
          "Philadelphia, Pennsylvania"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following is the oldest city in the United States?",
        "tags": [
          "history",
          "usa",
          "cities"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517ce",
        "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Richard I",
          "William the Conqueror",
          "Alfred the Great"
        ],
        "question": "Which English king was given the title 'Defender Of The Faith' by Pope Leo X?",
        "tags": [
          "leaders",
          "uk",
          "christianity",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9519b8",
        "correctAnswer": "Manhattan Island",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Moon",
          "The Last Dodo",
          "Queen Elizabeth's Corpse"
        ],
        "question": "What did Peter Minuit buy in 1626?",
        "tags": [
          "people",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518ca",
        "correctAnswer": "India",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Thailand",
          "Persia",
          "Turkey"
        ],
        "question": "What was the most Eastern land in Alexander The Great's command at his peak?",
        "tags": [
          "ancient_greece",
          "leaders",
          "the_ancient_world",
          "empires",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "64626287ab138b829b81ea10",
        "correctAnswer": "Battle of the Bulge",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Invasion of Normandy",
          "Battle of Stalingrad",
          "Pearl Harbor"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the 1944 German counteroffensive that was beaten back by allied units?",
        "tags": [
          "world_war_2",
          "military",
          "wars",
          "1940's",
          "history",
          "battles"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9519b7",
        "correctAnswer": "Washington D.C.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Atlanta",
          "San Francisco",
          "Denver"
        ],
        "question": "Which US City Did British Troops Invade and Burn In 1814?",
        "tags": [
          "usa",
          "wars",
          "cities",
          "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "638c77ea01e1a2ef6d1f146e",
        "correctAnswer": "Priscilla",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Francesca",
          "Lisa Marie",
          "Glady"
        ],
        "question": "What was Elvis Presley's wife's name?",
        "tags": [
          "elvis_presley"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950dc1",
        "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Rolling Stones",
          "Oasis",
          "Simon & Garfunkel"
        ],
        "question": "Which band did Paul McCartney belong to?",
        "tags": [
          "music",
          "bands",
          "musicians"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c71",
        "correctAnswer": "U2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Public Image Ltd.",
          "The Script",
          "The Cure"
        ],
        "question": "Which Irish rock band released the studio album 'The Unforgettable Fire'?",
        "tags": [
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fddd",
        "correctAnswer": "Barbra Streisand",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Madonna",
          "Hilary Duff",
          "Aretha Franklin"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer starred in the film 'Hello, Dolly!'?",
        "tags": [
          "film",
          "acting",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ca1",
        "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Wings",
          "Rudimental",
          "The Alan Parsons Project"
        ],
        "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'See Emily Play'?",
        "tags": [
          "rock_music",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94feb6",
        "correctAnswer": "Beyoncé",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Madonna",
          "Drake",
          "Nicki Minaj"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer, actress and record producer released the studio album 'B'Day'?",
        "tags": [
          "music_albums",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "64adcb300d501be39aa6c78a",
        "correctAnswer": "A loser",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "An idiot",
          "A dweeb",
          "A sucker"
        ],
        "question": "What does Beck refer to himself as in one of his songs?",
        "tags": [
          "songs",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94feee",
        "correctAnswer": "David Bowie",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Eric Clapton",
          "Madonna",
          "Mika"
        ],
        "question": "Which musician released the album '\"Heroes\"'?",
        "tags": [
          "music_albums",
          "musicians",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "625064b4e12f6dec240bdfc7",
        "correctAnswer": "Safety Dance",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "What's Up",
          "Bitch",
          "I Know What Boys Like"
        ],
        "question": "What song did Men Without Hats have a hit with in 1983?",
        "tags": [
          "songs",
          "one_hit_wonders",
          "1980's",
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      },
      {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c44",
        "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Swans",
          "The Velvet Underground",
          "Aerosmith"
        ],
        "question": "Which American rock band released the song 'Good Vibrations'?",
        "tags": [
          "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
      }
    
    

]